BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19)
1969-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/019
41 cubic feet
41 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
7256708
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Getzel, April 26, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective bargaining -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Paper industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Building trades -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Iron and steel workers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Teachers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Nurses -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Service industries -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Automobile industry and trade -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Communication and traffic -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Public employees -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Engineers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Fire fighters -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Police -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Transportation -- United States; United States.; United States. Dept. of Labor; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics
7256708
- Code no.810007: Omaha (municipal employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Omaha City Employees, Local 251, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.810010: Anaheim City School District (certificated) and National Education Association / Anaheim Elementary Education Association, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.810012: San Jose (clerical and support staff) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 101, 1995- 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.810032: Boston (clerks & technicians) and Service Employees International Union, Local 888, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.810041: New York, City University of (faculty) and American Federation of Teachers / American Association of University Professors, Professional Staff Congress 2334, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.810051: Sacramento, City (operations & maintenance; office & technical; professional) and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 39, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.810064: Memphis (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1733, 1989- 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.810084: Baltimore City (white collar) and American Federation of Teachers / City Union of Baltimore, Local 800, 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.810085: Seattle (joint crAmerican Federation of Teacherss-nonsupervisory) and Various, 1995-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.810108: Milwaukee City (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 48, 1997- 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.810132: Detroit, City of (non-supervisory) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 25, 1995- 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.810137: Boston (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 93, 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.810164: Hurley Medical Center (clerical and technical) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1603, Co. 25, 1988-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.810166: Boston (police dept.) and International Union of Police Associations / Boston Police Patrolmen's Association, 1993- 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.810179: Seattle (professional, technical, business & administrative support units) and Union of Professional and Technical Employees, Local 17, 1994-2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.810181: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (social services) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1972-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code no.810182: Elizabeth NJ City Board of Education and National Education Association / Elizabeth Education Association, 1996- 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code no.810183: Waukesha, School District of (teachers) and National Education Association / Education Association of Waukesha, 1995- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code no.810184: Appleton Area WI School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Appleton Education Association, 1999- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Code no.810185: Rochester MN Independant School District 535 (teachers) and National Education Association / Rochester Education Association, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code no.810190: Rockford IL Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Rockford Education Association, 1996- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code no.810191: Salem OR Board of Education (classified) and Salem-Keizer Association of Classified Employees, 1995-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Code no.810192: Indiana University (service, maintenance & food service) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 832, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code no.810302: Milwaukee City (police) and International Union of Police Associations, Local 21, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code no.810443: New York City Sanitation Dept (sanitation officers) and Service Employees International Union, SOA 444, 1978- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code no.810444: New York City (traffic enforcement) and Communication Workers of America, Local 1181, Local 1182, 2002-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Code no.810445: New York City (principle administrative assocociates) and Communication Workers of America, Local 1180, 1992- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Code no.810446: New York City (mechanics and machinists) and Service Employees International Union, Local 246, 1991-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code no.810454: Anaheim (Convention Center employees) and Service Employees International Union, Local 399, Local 952, 1986- 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Code no.810456: New York City (fire dept.--fire officers) and International Association of Fire Fighters / Uniformed Fire Officers Association, 1984-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Code no.810460: New York City (clerical) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Code no.810482: Baltimore City (trades) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 67, Local 44, 1997- 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Code no.810492: Boston (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 718, 1987-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code no.810505: Cincinnati, City of (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 8, 1998- 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code no.810506: Columbus, City of (municipal employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1632, 1999-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code no.810507: Cleveland, City of (municipal employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 100, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code no.810508: Cincinnati, University of (clerical employees) and Service Employees International Union, Local 1199, 1999-2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code no.810570: Toledo (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1993-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code no.810571: Montgomery County (police officers) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 35, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code no.810591: New York City (fire dept.--firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters / Uniformed Firefighters' Association, 1995- 2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code no.810598: Rochester NY (municipal employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1635, 1994- 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code no.810599: District of Columbia (comp units 1 & 2) and Various, 1977-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code no.810611: Philadelphia (police dept.) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 5, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code no.810612: Milwaukee City (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 215, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code no.810613: Pittsburgh (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters / Pitsburgh Firefighters Local 1, 1978-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Code no.810619: Baltimore City (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 734, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code no.810621: Philadelphia (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 22, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code no.810632: Detroit, City of (drivers & others) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 214, 1989-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code no.810635: Seattle (police officers) and Seattle Police Officers' Guild, 1991-2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code no.810636: Jacksonville FL (police officers-sergeants) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 5-30, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code no.810637: Seattle Police Dept (police management) and Seattle Police Management Association, 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code no.810643: Portland OR (clerical & maintenance) and District Council of Trade Unions, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code no.810646: Jacksonville FL (municipal unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 79, 1997- 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code no.810647: Baltimore City (professionals & supervisors) and Managerial and Professional Society of Baltimore, Inc., 1988- 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code no.810648: Detroit, City of (police dept.) and Detroit Police Officers Association, 1998-2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code no.810649: Osceola County FL Public Schools (teachers) and Osceola County Teachers Association, 1993-2006 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Code no.810655: Oakland, City of (units B-D) and Service Employees International Union / United Public Employess, Local 790, 1988- 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Code no.810656: Dade County (professionals) and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 100, 1995-2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Code no.810657: Dade County (supervisors) and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 100, 1993-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Code no.810658: Jacksonville FL (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 122, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Code no.810660: New York City, Sanitation Deptartment (sanitation workers) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, USA Local 831, 1978-2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Code no.810661: Nashville & Davidson County, Metro Government of (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 5, 1995- 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Code no.810662: New York City Board of Education (counselors) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1995-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code no.810663: New York City Board of Education (secretaries) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1991-2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code no.810664: New York City Board of Education (social workers & psychologists) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1991-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code no.810669: Elgin IL School District (teachers) and National Education Association, Local 46, 1991-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code no.810675: Cincinnati, University of (faculty) and American Association of University Professors, Cincinnati Chapter, 1989-2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code no.810748: Detroit, City of (police-sergeants & lieutenants) and Detroit Police Lieutenants and Sergeants Association, 1992- 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code no.810749: Oklahoma City (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 157, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code no.810750: Oklahoma City (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 123, 1996-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code no.811055: District of Columbia (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 36, 1977-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code no.811116: District of Columbia (corrections) and Fraternal Order of Police, 1974-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code no.811138: San Jose (peace officers) and San Jose Police Officers Association, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Code no.811146: Dayton, City of (clerical & technical) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 101, 1988-2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code no.811152: New York City (motor vehicle operators) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 982, 1990-2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Code no.811191: Las Vegas City (general unit) and Las Vegas City Employees' Association, 1988-2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Code no.811202: Detroit, City of (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 344, 1992-2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Code no.811212: Pittsburgh (police dept.) and Fraternal Order of Police, 1996-2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Code no.811213: Iowa State Board of Regents (health care) and Service Employees International Union, Local 199, 1996-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Code no.811214: Jefferson County (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2629, 2001- 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code no.811251: Connecticut, University of (professionals) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 3695, 1980-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code no.811265: Philadelphia (professional & clerical) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 47, 1988-1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code no.811276: Memphis Light, Gas & Water Div (nonsupervisory) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1288, 1978-2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code no.811280: Florida State (doctors & dentists) and Federation of Physicians and Dentists, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code no.811284: St. Petersburg FL (blue collar unit) and Service Employees International Union, 1994-2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Code no.811286: Philadelphia Board of Educucaton (food service) and UNITE HERE, Local 634, 1995-2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code no.811288: Hempstead NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 880, 1993- 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Code no.811290: Stockton Unified School District (unit A-general services) and Service Employees International Union /California School Employees Association, Ch. 318, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code no.811292: Stockton Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Stockton Teachers Association, 1994- 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Code no.811294: Service Employees International Union, Local 715, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Code no.811296: Pennsylvania State (supervisors-social workers) and Service Employees International Union, Local 668, 1996-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Code no.811314: New York City (real estate unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 2000- 2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Code no.811320: Connecticut State (educational professionals-unit P3B) and Service Employees International Union / Connecticut State Employees Association, 1993-2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Code no.811321: Connecticut State (engineers, scientists-unit P4) and Service Employees International Union / Connecticut State Employees Association, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Code no.811322: Oregon State (Fairview Training Center - non-guard unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1246, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Code no.811323: Oregon State (corrections - security) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1994- 2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code no.811324: Multnomah CN S.D. #1--Portland (classified) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 111, 1999-2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code no.811325: Federal Way WA School District (teachers & rel) and Federal Way Employees Association, 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code no.811331: Albuquerque, City of (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 624, 1988- 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code no.811425: Glendale City CA (general) and GCEA-I, 1994-2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Code no.811431: New York City Health and Hospital Corporation (hospital technicians) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC37 / Service Employees International Union, Local 1199 / International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local, 2008-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Code no.811432: New York City (accountants & edp) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Code no.811433: New York City (seasonal) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Code no.811434: New York City (health services--Unit F) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1995- 2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Code no.811435: New York City Health & Hospital Corporaton (institutional services, Unit B) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1982-2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Code no.811436: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (auto service workers) and Service Employees International Union, Local 246, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Code no.811442: Naperville IL School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1991-2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Code no.811464: New York City (off-track betting) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2021, 1987- 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Code no.811470: New York City Transit Authority (clerical, office, motor) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1988-2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Code no.811471: Collier County FL School Board (office, classroom support) and National Education Association / Collier County Association of Educational Office and Classroom Assistant Personnel, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Code no.811472: New York City Health and Hospital Corporation (analysts) and Organization of Staff Analysts, 1995-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Code no.811475: New York City (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1990- 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Code no.811484: Columbus, City of (police dept.) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 9, 1990-2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Code no.811490: Tampa (general unit) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1464, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Code no.811551: Wichita City (multi-department) and Service Employees International Union, Local 513, 1980-1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Code no.811620: Hillsborough County FL Board of Education (classified-bc) and American Federation of Teachers / Hillsborough School Employee Association, Local 167, 1995-2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Code no.811621: Cincinnati, City of (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 48, 1998-2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Code no.811630: Palm Beach County School District (clerical) and Association of Education Secretaries and Office Professionals, 1997- 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Code no.811635: Sacramento County (welfare unit) and United Public Employees, Local 1, 1994-2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Code no.811689: Buffalo (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, PBFA 282, 1977-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Code no.811714: Phoenix (office and clerical) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1994-2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Code no.811715: Phoenix (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2960, 1986- 2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Code no.811779: Cincinnati, City of (police dept.) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 69, 1995-2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Code no.811808: New York City Board of Education (cross guards) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Code no.811811: Tucson Board of Education (white collar, food service) and National Education Association / Tucsan Education Association, 1991-2003 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Code no.811821: Los Angeles City (safety, security, & nonsworn) and Service Employees International Union, Local 347, 1994- 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Code no.811822: Los Angeles City (building trades) MOU #2 and Los Angeles Building and Construction Trades Council, 1995- 2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Code no.811823: Phoenix (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 493, 1988-2004 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Code no.811824: Providence RI (public service employees) and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 1033, 1995- 2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Code no.811825: Los Angeles City (technical unit) and Engineers and Architects Association, 1994-2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Code no.811826: Los Angeles City (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 112, 1994-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Code no.811827: Los Angeles City (clerical & support services) MOU # 3 and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 3090, 1991-2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Code no.811828: Los Angeles City (service and crafts) and Service Employees International Union, Local 347, 1994-2004 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Code no.811829: Los Angeles City (equipment operators & laborers) and Service Employees International Union, Local 347, 1994- 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Code no.811830: Los Angeles City (police officers) and Los Angeles Police Protective League, 1985-2005 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Code no.811831: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (clinicians) and Service Employees International Union, 1984- 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Code no.811832: Phoenix (police) and International Union of Police Associations / Phoenix Law Enforcement Association, 1998- 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Code no.811833: New York City (engineers & scientists) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)